[{"answer": "Are you going away for the weekend", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Moving out?", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You mean somebody wants to lure us into a trap...", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Kill you", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "After performance, there will be little celebration backstage", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " You are invited, also", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "For services you will render", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I am not.   But Madame is", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I hoped I could avoid the subject. But some of us", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "The point is that my friend is not an isolated case", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " What's going on? What happened to the girls", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What way", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "For what", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What young lady", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Maildrops and canaries and wheelchairs... And what was all that about my friend? And what do you suppose they're doing up there? And where is up there", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "One year before that place?    Think of that", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "that place, isn't it", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well, I can save you a lot of trouble", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "My suggestion is that you pursue it no further", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "my friend, what exactly are you up to", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "But what game? Are you really that interested in the Belgian engineer", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "It's about a mile out of town.  Why would you be wanting to go there", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "It's got a view, right enough", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yes. The castle is closed to the public while work is going on", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "It's being restored by the Society for the Preservation of Scottish Monuments", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Pleasant, but ignorant. He was off one hundred years and one my friend.  It's actually 1500 and my friend the Fourth", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "If he's an official guide", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Sorry to be so unobliging.  my friend... H'mm", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Speaking about things floating in the lake", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Aren't they rather small for sailors", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "They should make it a rule. It's quite fatiguing to pin on all those medals while standing on our toes", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "If there's one thing I dislike about the British, it's their climate. I understand your jails are quite damp", "docId": "Private-Life-of-Sherlock-Holmes_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 34}]